(Sheldon:)I love the turn-by-turn voice option.
Has it really only been 10 miles?
(Leonard:)I'm turning it on, but just to shut you up.
(Sheldon:)Leonard,
bear left and continue on Interstate 210.
(Sheldon:)Ooh, sounds like that fellow
knows what he's talking about.
(Sheldon:)I'd put on my listening ears if I were you.
- What did you do?
- I found a hack online.
(Sheldon:)I was able to upload MP3 recordings
of my voice to your GPS.
- That is so cool.
- Counterpoint, no, it's not.
(GPS:)Continue on Interstate 210 for five miles.
(GPS:)Here's an interesting fact
about Interstates:
- Really?
- Shh!
(Sheldon:)He said it's interesting.
Interstates are numbered as follows:
(GPS:)Even-numbered routes run east and west.
(GPS:)Odd-numbered routes run
north and south.